<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="hello">Hello World, Ultra_Fare_calculater9Activity!</string>
    <string name="app_name">UltraFareCalculator</string>
<string name="about">
        END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT

IMPORTANT READ CAREFULLY: This End-User License Agreement ("EULA") is a legal agreement between you (either an individual person or a single legal entity, who will be referred to in this EULA as "You") and the Licensor for the UltraFareCalculator9 that displays this EULA, including any associated media, printed materials and electronic documentation (the "Software"). The Software also includes any software updates, add-on components, and/or supplements that the Licensor may provide to You or make available to You after the date You obtain Your initial copy of the Software to the extent that such items are not accompanied by a separate license agreement or terms of use. By installing, copying, downloading, accessing or otherwise using the Software, You agree to be bound by the terms of this EULA. If You do not agree to the terms of this EULA, do not install, access or use the Software. 
For purposes of this EULA, the term "Licensor" refers to UltraNEO, except in the event that You acquired the Software as a component of a ULTRANEO software product originally licensed from the manufacturer of your computer system or computer system component, then "Licensor" or refers to such hardware manufacturer. By installing, copying, downloading, accessing or otherwise using the Software, You agree to be bound by the terms of this EULA. If You do not agree to the terms of this EULA, Licensor is unwilling to license the Software. In such event, You may not install, copy, download or otherwise use the Software. 

NOTE: IF YOU DO NOT HAVE A VALID LICENSE FOR THIS SOFTWARE PRODUCT, YOU ARE NOT AUTHORIZED TO INSTALL, COPY OR OTHERWISE USE THE SOFTWARE. 
 
SOFTWARE LICENSE 
The Software is protected by intellectual property laws and treaties. The Software is licensed, not sold. 

        
    </string>
</resources>